{
    "subject": "resource/Hack_Schumann",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Buffalo,_New_York",
    "human_readable": "Hack Schumann was born in Buffalo, New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8825643062591553,
            "question": "Where was Hack Schumann born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8109185695648193,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Buffalo, New York besides Hack Schumann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.796649158000946,
            "question": "When was Hack Schumann born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4200695753097534,
            "question": "Do any historical events connect to Hack Schumann's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39661309123039246,
            "question": "What state is Buffalo, New York located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3069675862789154,
            "question": "Is Hack Schumann known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27825847268104553,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks in Buffalo, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22299399971961975,
            "question": "What is the population of Buffalo, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21408838033676147,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Buffalo, New York's culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12641246616840363,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Buffalo, New York?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hack Schumann was born in Buffalo, New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1332_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about Buffalo, New York's culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1332_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Buffalo, New York?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1332_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable landmarks in Buffalo, New York?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1332_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1332_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Charles J. \"Hack\" Schumann (also referred to as Hack Schumann) was born on August 13, 1884, in Buffalo, New York, United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Hack Schumann was born on August 13, 1884, in Buffalo, New York, United States. Therefore, the statement \"Hack Schumann was born in Buffalo, New York\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}